http://www.mvssolutions.com/privacy.html

Privacy Statement
Commitment To Your Privacy
This site is owned and operated by MVS Solutions
Incorporated. Your privacy on the Internet is of utmost importance to
us.
MVS Solutions Incorporated has created
this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to
online and internet privacy. The following discloses our information
gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: www.mvssolutions.com.
Cookies
Our site does not use cookies.
A cookie is a small data file that
certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie
file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to
track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a
cookie can contain is information that you supply yourself. A cookie
can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other
sites.
From time to time we may use an outside ad company
to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be
coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from the outside
companies who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies
nor do we have access to any information about you from cookies you
might receive from other companies while visiting our site or while
visiting any other web site.
For more information on cookies, visit Cookie Central.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that MVS
Solutions Incorporated is not responsible for the privacy practices
of such other sites. We encourage our visitors and users to be aware
when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each
and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this
Web Site.
Information Collection and Use
MVS Solutions Incorporated is the sole owner of the information collected
on this site. We will not sell or rent the information collected on
this site without your prior consent. MVS Solutions Incorporated collects
information from our users at several different points on our web site.
On certain pages such as the Contact
Form Submissions Page, we give visitors and users the option of providing
us with names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and other
information and various details regarding how MVS may be of assistance
to our visitors. We do not gather this information without the users´
knowing and active permission and participation.
On certain other pages such as the
Ezine Subscribe Page, we give visitors and users the option of subscribing
to our email-based publication The Business of ScienceTM. The visitor
and user has the option of subscribing to our publication by providing
us with their email address. We also provide existing subscribers to
The Business of ScienceTM the option of unsubscribing to the e-zine.
We do not gather this information without the users´ knowing and active
permission and participation.
Using the Recommend This Site link
and page, we give visitors and users the option of sending an email
recommending MVS's website and webpages to friends, colleagues and family
members. The visitor and user has the option of providing their name
and email address as well as the name and email address of the recipient
being sent the recommendation.. We do not gather this information without
the users´ knowing and active permission and participation.
We use log files and web site statistics with IP addresses to analyze
trends, administer the site, track user´s movement, and gather broad
demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked
to personally identifiable information.
Security
This web site takes every precaution to protect the information provided
by visitors to our site. When visitors submit information to MVS Solutions
Incorporated via the web site or Internet, your information is protected
both online and off-line. All of our visitors´ information is restricted
in our offices.
If you have any
questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email
to security@mvssolutions.com.
Internet Content
MVS Solutions adheres to the internet content ratings of the ICRA. The ICRA (Internet Content Rating Association) is an international non-profit organization supporting the protection of children from potentially harmful material while also protecting free speech on the internet.
Our
website has been labelled with ICRA.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this
privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with
this Web Site, you can contact:
Dr. Louis M. Scarmoutzos
MVS Solutions Incorporated
340 Main Street, Suite 204
Melrose, MA 02176-4662 USA
mvs@mvssolutions.com
For more information about internet privacy and protecting your privacy
online, visit The TRUSTe Organization:
Visit MVSSolutions.com for info about our technology development services. Visit MVSSolutions.biz for info about our enterprise development & business services. Visit MVSSolutions.us for info about our government contractor services.
Conducting
the Business of Science SM
HOME | WHO WE ARE | WHAT WE DO | AFFILIATIONS | CONTACT
US | PRIVACY STATEMENT | JOBS | NEWS
CAPABILITIES | SITE MAP | COPYRIGHT
AND TRADEMARK NOTICE | THE BUSINESS OF SCIENCE
TECHNICAL
DUE DILIGENCE |
QUICK TOOLS
Resources:
Biotech | Chemistry | Medical Devices | Materials | Environmental | Engineering | Pharmaceutical | Green Chemistry |
Technology Marketplace | Strategic Alliances & Partnering | Venture Capital & Funding | Grant Opportunities | Business | General | International | Search | Publications | Homeland Security | Web Directory | The Business of Science Newsletter
EMAIL
Deutsch | English | Español | Français | Italiano |
Português
© 1999-2006
MVS Solutions Incorporated. All Rights Reserved.
